An adventurous race against time!
Once Upon a Forest is a animation, family, adventure
film directed by Charles Grosvenor.
A young mouse, mole and hedgehog risk their lives to find a cure
for their badger friend, who's been poisoned by men.
Cornelius (voice), played by Michael Crawford.
Phineas (voice), played by Ben Vereen.
Abigail (voice), played by Ellen Blain.
Edgar (voice), played by Benji Gregory.
Russell (voice), played by Paige Gosney.
Michelle (voice), played by Elisabeth Moss.
Once Upon a Forest is a 1993 animated adventure film produced by
Hanna-Barbera and distributed by 20th Century Fox.
Based on the Furlings characters created by Rae Lambert, the film was directed by Charles Grosvenor and
produced by David Kirschner, and stars the voices of Michael Crawford and Ben Vereen.
The film is about a trio of "Furlings" – the story's term for young anthropomorphic
animals – who go on an expedition to find a cure for their poisoned friend.
The film's environmental theme divided critics at the time of
its release, along with the animation and story.
The film grossed $6.6 million in the US against a budget of $13–16 million.
The film explores themes of friendship, animals, quest.